CLSA's view on the bank is that
it has remained intact. The
bank has taken about 400 from the subscriber and will
show from here that it is going to come into the bank. A
lot of credit has to be given to the subscriber. The
management does
not think that
it will remain intact
and has shown
hatred towards others and
then they felt that on
Thursday
night it will help you somewhere. It will be
visible in the profits and growth of GPS
because the border work itself is tremendous
and going forward, you will see a tremendous increase in the order book year after year in the next one or two
quarters.
Today, he will tell his target
price higher here. In the
changes that are coming from the government in the telecom sector, the
strategy of the British is visible and this
record is visible in Bharti Airtel but for those Vodafone
Idea, you are in trouble.
Find out according to the problem here.
Subscribers have said that the government has done this
for the entire sector. We have 4 pages now
and let's start from UP Gate.
Today, they believe that Vodafone Idea's
e-payment is going to save about 10 to 12 thousand
crores per annum. These people can do it on impact.  You
can use it to improve your telecom network due to which 2-inch market
share is being launched, it is threatening in the market,
apart from this, for India also you may have to
take a decision of about 10 to 11 thousand rupees that you
can do this, that option is
even like their
item
subscription
but it seems that this is
definitely terrifying to you, they will show you the
tattoo designs of the companies according to the yagnas,
in the upcoming account you will see five options, so those who are in
debt
sector, this will give you an interim relief from the
government and this is
positive news for the telecom sector, jhal jhal jhal